<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sumner Web Design - A portfolio site</title>
    <description>A portfolio site with work examples and collection of resources.</description>
    <link>#/</link>
    <atom:link href="#/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 17:18:55 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 17:18:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack 198</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I developed a web site for Cub Scout Pack 198 in Portland, Oregon.  It was built using PHP and Sass with Compass.  I utilized modern CSS such as flex boxes and gradients to create a modern, mobile first site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to integrate user registration for parents of scouts, photo and video upload by registered users, and a roster that is built from the registration information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site be placed on the pack’s domain once we have access to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://vetsrights.com&quot;&gt;Cub Scout Pack 198&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>#/Pack-198</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">#/Pack-198</guid>
        
        
        <category>sites</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bible Word Study</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://biblewordstudy.net&quot;&gt;Bible Word Study&lt;/a&gt; is a site I developed using the Joomla CMS and the Helix 3 framework.  It is a full featured site with a forum, blog, calendar, and articles.  The forum and calendars have a mix of private and public sections so private information can be shared with specific groups as well as having public interaction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>#/Bible-Word-Study</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">#/Bible-Word-Study</guid>
        
        
        <category>sites</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the beginning of the adventure with Jekyll and GitHub’s hosting service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the site is twofold.  First, it will serve as a portfolio.  Second, I will use this as a repository for code snips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope your find it interesting.  Feel free to make additions in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 07:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>#/Initial-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">#/Initial-post</guid>
        
        
        <category>sites</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
